hi and today on Polar Ice Creamery we
are going to make Kinder Bueno ice cream
but we're not just going to take some of
these and chop them up and put them in
the base cuz that's what most people do
we're going to go a little bit further
and do something a little bit different
with it so if you want to see what we're
going to
do let's get on with
[Music]
it yeah most people on the internet you
know in in all of its Glory do Kinder
Bueno ice cream by just making a vanilla
ice cream base and then chopping up
these and putting them in um and they
also do that with no churn bases I'm
going to do a no churn video cuz that
seems to be the one that you voted for
in our poll on here on YouTube but for
now if you've watched this channel
enough you know that I don't just do
simple ice creams I do some complicated
ones some way too complicated but
Kinder Bueno ice cream it it is what is
it let's look at the pack it's a creamy
hazelnut filling covered in smooth milk
chocolate with Crispy wafer as well
inside so we've got
Hazelnut and milk chocolate are are
deciding flavors crispy wafer can we do
something with Crispy wafer I mean it
has no taste of the
wafer it's kind of it's just a vessel to
hold the creamy filling so maybe we just
scrap that what we're going to
do is a hazelnut ice cream we're going
to recreate the filling that's in the
Kinder Bueno we're going to do a
chocolate swirl probably through the ice
cream itself and top I think with
that creamy hazelnut filling first thing
we're going to do
is create the hazelnut
filling so let's get one of these out
the
pack
here it's like
a taupey colored khy
colored hazel nut feeling it's quite
sweet
so for the filling we've got some
hazelnuts here we're going to roast them
in the oven and make that up so let's
turn the oven on and get those roasting
while we then deal with our ice cream
components set the oven to
325f and let's get a little
pan and we're going to get our hazelnuts
in there all got the skins on we don't
really want the
Skins
so we're just going to roast these hazer
nuts in the oven for about 10 to 15
minutes so let's get on with the ice
cream base and for the ice cream base
you are going to need 830 G of milk 740
G of cream this is whipping cream at 33%
220 g of sugar 60 G of glucose syrup or
corn syrup 120 g of skin milk powder if
you're going to use stabilizer it's 3 to
3 and 1/2
G and our hazelnut extract we're going
to use 5 to 10 G now that's quite a A
variation but they're not all created
equal some are very weak some are very
strong so if it's a very strong one just
use five if it's a very weak one then
you might want to use 10 let's we out
our ingredients
830 we're going to need a bigger
pan there we go you can Harve this
recipe if you want it's absolutely fine
you don't need to follow these amounts
um just divide everything by two it's
very very simple a
740 of
cream just like that 2 20 g of
sugar 20 G left in here and if you're
wondering
what we do this for it's the stabilizer
because this is a large
batch I can't eat it all in one go and
it's just too much
to consume in a few days so I use
stabilizer this enables me to make sure
that the ice cream is as good as it can
possibly be for a a reasonable length of
time don't confuse stabilizer with
artificial
ingredients this is just you're going
through the effort of
making you know a luxury ice cream
that's why you're here on this channel
let's let's be fair that's why you're
here because you want to make the best
ice cream you can
make so if you can use a stabilizer it
will remain the best ice cream that you
can make for a longer period of time it
won't last
forever but it will last a good
while so just mixing up our stabilizer
and our sugar and we're going to put
that in there as
well okay now we've only got a couple of
things left to add which are our skin
milk powder
and our corn syrup so let's get that
in 60 G if you want to
use there there we go if you want to use
glucose syrup go for it essentially you
just want an invert sugar 120 g of skim
milk powder
do not
use high fructose corn
syrup because your ice cream probably
won't freeze very well there we've got
our milk our cream our sugar our corn
syrup our skin milk powder we're going
to leave the extract until we finished
Heating
and let's get it on
hob this is really simple we've just got
the hob on a medium heat and we're just
going to stir all this in once it comes
up to to the temperature that your
stabilizer needs for me that 75 to 80°
Centigrade which is this in
fah you're going to take it off the heat
put it in a container and pop it in the
fridge for a good 3 to 4
hours oh that's warm on our hands there
we go right Skins are really nicely
cracked we want a little bit of color
let me show you
what the skins of the hazut look like
don't be afraid of getting them to this
stage okay steaming up the camera here
because we want those skins to come off
underneath beautiful color very
hot that's what we want the Haz nuts to
be like if you don't toast them
enough the Skins just don't come off
very well okay so what we now want to do
is just get the skins off okay so nice
and
[Music]
easy take a
container put them in get the
escapes lid on Shake
[Applause]
it perfect if you got one or two like
that that the skin just doesn't want to
come off of don't stress about it the
majority of these look like that okay
they're still lovely we we don't mind a
little bit of color and some skins won't
come
off nuts particularly easily and that's
the amount of oil that is in the nut so
don't stress your little s about it
right we need to get those nuts out of
there we've got our blender
here so we want to get all of these
lovely hazer nuts into
here they're still very hot if you do it
like this so just be careful I have
asbestos
fingers so I'm not particularly bothered
about it hazelnuts in they're they're
chirping away that's the cooling process
as they cool down they they shrink and
that creates that kind of cracking sound
so we need to blend these up but before
we do that we're just going to let them
sit there for a minute we need our
chocolate so we've got 100 G of
hazelnuts here we're going to need some
chocolate this is white chocolate it's
good quality chocolate this is
calbo you can buy it in
Safeways so we're going to take 100 G
and into that white chocolate we are
also going to good teaspoon of our
deodorized coconut oil deodorized
coconut oil is also called refined
coconut oil it what it does is takes the
Flor Flor of coconut out we don't want
that in the microwave 10c stints
stirring it as you go until the
chocolate is completely melted and we've
got a nice smooth paste that took about
a minute give or
take there's um just a couple of small
little pieces in there you can just keep
stirring that until that dissolves so
now we're going to make noise we're
going to Blitz up the hazel nuts and
when it's into a paste we're going to
add in our white chocolate okay so you
don't need the mic for that cuz it's
very very
[Music]
loud tastes
delicious and that is pretty much it
until we get to the chain stage so I'll
see you in a few
[Music]
hours
white chocolate Okay into that we are
going to
add again we're going to go for a
good amount of our refined coconut oil
this time we're going to
use a little bit
more that's almost two teaspoons so it's
just over 10
G of that let's get that in the
microwave and get it
melted so now that it's
melted in the
microwave nice smooth white chocolate
we've got our coconut oil in there we're
going to use our hazelnut
extract it's good stuff you don't need a
lot you just need about half a teaspoon
to 165 g of chocolate Okay stir that
in if you don't have the coconut oil in
there you run the risk of that chocolate
seasoning that's bang on the money that
one and we finally we just want to add
5 g 1 teaspoon of corn
syrup that's
good that is also going to go in the
fridge and we're going to come back in
an hour or two to churn the ice
cream so with your ice cream base
chilled you're going to take it out the
fridge and add in your hazelnut extract
make sure it's nicely mixed in and then
pop it in your ice cream machine take
your hazelnut butter and your hazut
cream out the fridge we need those to
come up to temperature now instead of
the chocolate sauce I'm actually going
to do like a chocolate Strat Strater so
we're going to take some of our semi
chocolate add some coconut oil into
there and gently warm it in the
microwave until it's completely melted
now in the final minute or two of
churning you're going to pour in half of
your chocolate mixture I've used about
50 g here in total and just let that
churn up for a few minutes until it's
ready and then what you're going to do
is start loading up your ice cream
container so you're going to start with
one good solid scoop of the ice cream
and then into that you are going to take
your hazelnut butter and pour some of
that in
there and continue with that until your
tub is completely full and at that stage
you're going to take some of your really
lovely Kinder Bueno hazelnut
cream and you're going to pour pour it
gently over the top of the ice cream
until there's a thin layer of the
hazelnut cream itself that will go hard
in the freezer but before you put it in
the freezer just finally top it with the
remaining semi chocolate drizzle and
that will blend into that hazelnut cream
nicely finally put it in the freezer for
4 to 5 hours to harden
off ice cream has been in the fridge for
a freezer for a while now so I I do know
what some of this tastes like because
you know we've eaten loads of
it
um let's get some dished up in here and
talk about
[Music]
it all right this is a relatively
complicated ice cream to make there's a
lot going into this but all the
individual components are actually quite
simple the the ice cream being hazelnut
flavored is delicious I mean there are
some bad hazelnut extracts out there but
majority of them are pretty pretty
decent to be
fair the chocolate Flex throughout as
well they just break up a nice texture
different element to it it's really
really nice the hazelnut paste now that
recipe is all over social media of
people saying this is exactly as Kinder
Bueno core is you know the the cream
inside it's really not it's not it just
happens that it's hazelnut flavored so
it's something that's smooth that's
hazelnut flavored and everyone thinks
it's the same it's not you want to make
the cream that's inside of Kinder Bueno
then just take your white chocolate
hazelnut extract a little bit of corn
syrup you're good to go that's it
nothing else needed super
smooth taste
identical so good that we actually all
ate it within you know 24 hours
but the hard chocolate top obviously Ben
and Jerry's do topped ice
cream Magnum do topped ice cream there's
others that do it as well once Ben and
Cherry's did it everyone wants to copy
so that's what we've done here we've got
that Kinder Bueno cream chocolate top
which is decorated again with the milk
chocolate swirled through it you got all
the elements let me just just grab
one all the
elements of a Kinder
Bueno open this
up we've got our milk chocolate outside
a dark
chocolate kind of line through it and
let's take a quick
bite and then inside we
have our hazelnut
cream and obviously the
wafer the wafer I just chose not to use
it doesn't do anything in the sweet
apart from being a vessel for the cream
itself and when you put Waf and ice
cream it it doesn't last doesn't stay
crispy goes soft very very quickly so by
having that
cream on the
top it just hits you with Kinder br I
know straight away so let's dive
in it's great
texture it's the right texture for a
really good ice
cream you got that hazut I'm going to
call it hazut butter you know it's the
same it's just it's peanut
butter with a couple of extra little
bits
but this ice cream is
delicious it's really really nice great
texture holds up well
quite a few different textures in there
from the hazelnut butter that has gone
semi hard you know with with the added
ingredients in there the white chocolate
there a lot of sugar and white chocolate
that means it's not quite as hard as
standard chocolate would go chocolate
Flex creamy ice cream chocolate top
what's not to like so we're big fans of
the Kinder buano ice cream in this house
if you are looking for a kinderart ice
cream that's actually good then I
suggest you try this one thanks very
much watching don't forget to like And
subscribe thank you to all my patreon
and Kofi supporters they're growing
numbers now I'll put a little list on
the side of the screen here of those
that do support the channel if you want
to support the channel then head over to
one of these locations and help out it
really helps me make these videos cuz
some of them cost quite a bit a fair bit
to make so so thanks for sticking with
us and we'll see you next time
[Music]